CURRICULUM VITAE - LUKAS ROSENBERGER

CONTACT DATA:

Address: Mühlweg 10

9560 Feldkirchen

Austria

Telephone: +43664 1644190

Email: lukas.rosenberger@hotmail.com

Portfolio: http://mr-rossi.github.io/



PERSONAL SUMMARY: Lukas Rosenberger is a Computer Science student, currently in his 4th

semester at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg. He is currently finishing his master thesis in MultiMediaTechnology, a modern blend of Computer Science and Media Technologies with a major focus on Video Game Engineering and Mixed Reality. Lukas is a passionate programmer who enjoys acquiring new knowledge and likes to keep up

with current developments in the gaming industry.

DATE OF BIRTH: 06 March 1994

EDUCATION:

09/2018 – present UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES SALZBURG

MultiMediaTechnology, MSc

09/2014 - 07/2018 UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES SALZBURG

MultiMediaTechnology, BSc

09/2008 - 07/2013 SECONDARY TECHNICAL VOCATIONAL COLLEGE AND INSTITUTE FOR

RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY VILLACHDepartment for Computer Sciences

Matura (with diploma)

Diploma: "SAP-Transaktionen vom Smartphone aus" (SAP transactions

on smartphones)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

10/2017 – 03/2018 APPLICATION DEVELOPER

Ilogs, Klagenfurt, Austria

07/2016 - 12/2016 **Internship (Game Development)**

Arkavis, Bangkok, Thailand

2015 SWITCH-APP

University of Natural Resources and Life Sciences, Vienna, Austria

07/2013 - 01/2014 **MILITARY SERVICE**

Hensel-Kaserne, Villach, Austria

07/2012 - 08/2012 **Internship + Diploma**

Supanz GmbH, Klagenfurt, Austria

Developing a mobile app to execute transactions in SAP systems

Lukas Rosenberger - +436641644190 - <u>lukas.rosenberger@hotmail.com</u> - <u>http://mr-rossi.github.io/</u>

CURRENT EXPERTISE:

Proficient in C++, C#, Java HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP; SQL, Oracle, SAP+ABAP;

Modern OpenGL, including Shader Programming in GLSL

Computer Vision

Basic 3D-modeling in Maya Linear Algebra and Statistics Software Architecture and Design Algorithms and Datastructures

Video Game Engineering

Experience with Unreal Engine and Unity

PERSONAL:

Nationality: Austrian

Languages: German (native),

English (First Certificate in English Grade A - C1),

Italian (basics)

Hobbies: 3D printing, Video Games, Pen&Paper RPGs

PERSONAL STATEMENT:

As an avid gamer and technology geek getting to study MultiMediaTechnology at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg is the perfect way of extending my personal hobbies into my future work

life.

I enjoy developing solutions to difficult problems and finding ways to improve on existing concepts. I can easily get excited about almost any kind of game project and will try to do everything possible to make games a great experience.

My focus is on game development and game design and I'm always trying to stay on top of new developments in those topics.

I have worked on several games, which you can find on my website http://mr-rossi.github.io/.

Ahr lef